♪ In the not
too distant future ♪
♪ somewhere in time and space ♪
♪ like nelson
and his robot pals ♪
♪ are caught
in an endless chase ♪
♪ pursued by a woman
whose name is pearl ♪
♪ an evil gal who wants
to rule the world ♪
♪ she threw a few things
in her purse ♪
♪ and her rocket ship
she hunts him all across
the universe ♪
I'll get you!
♪ I'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst I can find ♪
♪ la-la-la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ and I'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ la-la-la ♪
♪ now keep in mind,
mike can't control ♪
♪ where the movies
begin and end ♪
♪ he'll try to keep
his sanity ♪
♪ with the help
of his robot friends ♪
♪ robot role call ♪
You're on.
Oh, my stars.
Check me out.
I'm different.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts ♪
♪ la-la-la ♪
♪ just repeat to yourself ♪
♪ "it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really
just relax" ♪
♪ for... ♪
Well, hi, everyone.
Welcome to satellite of love.
[Both]
♪ here we come, a-wassailing ♪
♪ etcetera-etcetera ♪
Give us our wassail
if you'd please, sir.
Uh. Wassail?
I'm pretty sure
I'm fresh out of wassail.
Pff. You're no fun.
Come on, it's july.
I know,
but where's the challenge
in wassailing at christmas?
The place is lousy
with wassails.
Take two steps and-- bam!
You smash your toe
on tons of the lousy stuff!
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
What is wassail anyway?
- Oh. Um, well--
- it's, you know, it's, uh--
I don't know, I think it's
an anti-inflammatory
or something.
But the point is,
if you can't provide wassail
for wee humble tattered
minstrels,
you got to turn over
your debt card
and pin number immediately.
Yeah, it's a custom
that goes back centuries.
- You made that up.
- Na-uh.
Listen to the song.
[Both]
♪ if the person who you sing to
cannot provide the wassail ♪
♪ you are entitled to his
debt card and pin number ♪
♪ love and joy,
come to you ♪
♪ unless you cannot provide
the wassail ♪
♪ then severe
financial penalties ♪
♪ shall come to you ♪
♪ then severe financial
penalties to you ♪
Okay, that's the smurf brooch
with the diamond elves.
The porcelain cat,
and I think I like to order--
hold on, hold on.
I have wassail.
Hold on there, nelson.
Canned wassail?
No way, my friend.
Oh, yeah, I checked the lyrics
to your dumb little song.
And it doesn't say anything
about canned wassail.
Wait, let me see that there.
[Mutters]
Damn! He's right.
Nelson, you found a loop hole,
you rat.
Hold everything.
The castle's calling.
- [Gasps]
- And something's wrong.
Oh, you bet
there's something wrong.
The lawgiver
went on vacation
and left us
with a babysitter.
Look! Oh!
Why won't you play
with the blocks?
I don't want
to play with blocks.
It's insulting!
I have an infinite intellect.
I think you're
a little crabby,
and you might need a timeout
to think about it.
No. I can't stand timeouts.
The silence.
The desolation!
Okay, are you gonna
play nice with the blocks?
All right, steffi, you win.
This time.
You see?
It's horrible!
She calls me fluffy-kins.
And treats me like an animal!
Hey, did you chew this?
Um. Yes.
- No! No chew!
- [Chitters]
Man. There's hair everywhere.
Please don't treat me like this.
I'm a distinguished professor
of anthropology
from a future where apes
evolved from men.
No chew! No!
Go lie down.
Oh, okay.
Okay, which one of you
is mike?
Uh, that'd be me. Hi.
Okay, and which one of you
is servo
and which one of you is cow?
Um, I'm servo.
And I'm cow.
- Crow.
- What?
No, you're crow.
Yeah, I know.
Of course I'm crow.
I just said I'm crow,
you great feeb.
- Boy.
- Never mind.
He's crow.
Well, it says here I'm supposed
to send you a movie, right?
Um, excuse me, steffi.
Yes, brian.
No, it's brain.
I mean, brain guy.
I mean, observe--
never mind.
I'm finished,
and I'm going to my room
to commune with
the gossabanauthics
of the plangent dimension.
Well, it's four.
It says you take your
fruit snack at four.
I don't need to take
my fruit snack.
I will...
Because I want to.
Thank you.
Okay, guys,
your movie is called
the touch of satan.
Yuck.
And you--
you need another tick back.
[Chitters]
Enjoy the great taste
of wassail...
In cans.
- [Alarms wail]
- Hey, that's ours.
Come on, you big lug.
Oh, it's movie sign.
Oh, we got movie sign.
- Mmm.
- That is our wassail.
We worked hard for that.
You know what, guys?
I don't even think
you'd like it.
It's kind of skunky.
Well, check
the freshness date on it.
Let me see here.
Oh, there's the problem.
It says 1547.
Yeah, that's a pretty old
born-on date.
Hmm. I'll give
that ugly guy a call.
[Servo whistles]
Huh?
Uh, you know, I hope
the whole movie isn't lit
by a hurricane lantern.
[Man]
Oh, that darn hill
gets worse every time.
I here you, man. Moo.
I'll tell you.
[Grunts]
Come on, girl.
Don't stop now.
I already missed my tv.
[Mimics country accent]
And I don't care
if you're scared,
you can't sleep in the house.
Whoa. Whoa! Look out you guys!
Look out, duck!
Ow.
Woo, I must be getting old.
[Mimics country accent]
Why won't you lay any eggs?
Mercy,
if-- if you'd come in
like the rest of them,
there won't be all of this--
this chasing.
Yeah, milk me.
Oh, I can tell by the look
in your eye
that you like
all the fussing.
Well, just stand there
like a good girl.
Hello, tractor,
how are you this evening?
Well, hello pile of dung.
Now, what did I do
with that darn pitch fork?
Maybe the dag-blagit thing
is over yonder.
I know I left it in here
someplace.
[Cat meows]
All right, who's in here?
Oh, there's my
"walk me wet me susan".
Is that you, robert?
Robert the cat?
You're supposed to be in bed,
you little rascal.
With andrew the dog.
Now, where ever you are,
you better come out here.
When sore throat pain
strikes.
[Groans]
The american gothic people
take revenge.
[Laughs]
And then he died. Ha!
We'd laugh about it.
He might've been hurt.
[Servo sighs]
Aw, I'll get
more fresh blood.
Anybody want anymore coffee?
[Mumbles]
No thanks, not for me.
I'm going in to watch
the late news and go to bed.
Me either.
- It's open!
- [Chuckles]
- What's going on out there?
- Grandma kramer?
Lucinda! Get her in here!
Oh, my god, what is it?
What's the matter?
A kabuki actor's been hit.
Come on,
grandma dried apple head.
What happened?
What have you done?
I stayed in the tanning booth
for a whole decade.
Stop it.
Oh, look at the blood.
[All groan]
From now on, take your
bloody clothes off
on the porch please.
I-- I'm fine.
The last days
of edgar winter.
She's done it again.
Oh, we don't know.
- Don't we?
- 11 years.
And before that, nine.
And before that and that.
Oh, please, melissa.
Farmer square head.
I've got to do something.
This torment can't last forever.
You know that it can.
No. There's a way.
Right after this!
Ahh, the touch of satan.
Soften your hands
while you do the dishes.
♪♪ [Disco plays]
This is very 70's.
I'm guessing anthony zerbe
must be in this.
You know, I think
it's tony musante
as a kind of hip satan
who solves crimes.
Emby mellay?
That's not a name.
That's a bad scrabble hand.
[Servo mimics disco music]
With screwtape
on kettle drum.
Wormwood on harpsichord.
[Servo mimics disco music]
[All mimic disco music]
Okay, crow, I'm putting you
on clu gulager alert.
I'm on it, mike.
I take this very seriously.
All right.
[Servo mimics disco music]
- Oh, david spade as satan.
- That's good casting.
The vineyards
of ernest and julio satan.
Ha! Right.
Well, you know he's satan
'cause he didn't
signal his turn.
Spreading evil and hay fever
wherever he goes.
♪ When there's just ♪
♪ a touch of satan ♪
♪ in your heart ♪
He drives a maverick?
I would've put the prince
of darkness in a muscle car.
[Servo mimics trumpet]
♪ What do you get
when you fall from grace? ♪
♪ You only get cast
into perdition ♪
Ha! Good.
[Servo mimics trumpet]
There we go.
So long, foul deceiver.
Bon voyage, orneriest
spinner of lies!
Hasta la luego,
maverick-driving clootie!
- Yeah-- clootie?
- Clootie?
Yeah, it's scottish.
I looked it up.
- Huh. Okay.
- I did.
Odd disturbing score
co-written
by mike post
and igor stravinsky.
Sightsee on your own time,
beelzebub!
[Horn honks]
Get off the road, man goat!
Satan's harmonica band
lead by toots theilemans.
Well, he is
the master of torture.
He would have really long
credits like this.
Mike, behind that tree!
It's clu gulager!
- Where?
Oh, shoot,
it was monte markham.
I should resign my post.
I'm just not
doing a good job.
Thanks anyway,
appreciate it.
Thanks.
I should phone satan.
Tell him I'm gonna be
just a little late.
Hmm. What was
ann heche doing in there?
Citizen's arrest!
Oh, wait, I'm a cop.
Urgh. Just taking
a breather here.
I get really winded.
Nice looking town you got here.
You can't pay, can you?
Yeah? Well,
don't let the fool you, son.
More around here
that meets the eye.
No kidding.
Like what?
Well, look at what
I'm doing to your car.
Like murder, brother,
like murder.
- Murder?
- Yes siree bob.
Farmer down the road
got killed in his barn
by a pitch fork.
Happened a little over
a week ago.
Did they catch the guy yet?
No, I'm still at large.
Nope.
My money they won't either.
That'd be $6 even.
Oh, an extra dollar
for the aliens in my head.
You see, the way
I got it figured,
this job was done by one of them
phromicidal maniacs.
And we ain't got none of them
around here.
- Stamps?
- Uh, no thanks.
- Backrub?
Aw, come on.
Yup, long gone by now.
They won't catch him
until he kills again.
Being him, I should know.
You're right. Nobody needs--
what did you call it?
Phromicidal maniac.
Ha! That's even funnier
this time.
Yeah, nobody needs
a phromicidal maniac
hanging around.
Is that right? I should
check my diction-otimy.
Oh, what with all these
gas crises and watergates,
I needed a good laugh.
Hey, wait a minute.
The gas station guy
forgot to give me
my roman gabriel
cocktail glass.
Oh, no. The credits
are gonna unspool backwards now.
Huh. Let's have
a nice private place
to practice streaking.
Weren't they concerned about
holding an audience
back in the 70's at all,
I mean?
No, back then talkies
where still a novelty.
[Servo hums]
You know, I was just thinking
that gerald ford
is rather clumsy.
Thank you, lurch.
I'm gonna get out
my guitar and practice
"sister golden hair".
Well, I'm the first one
at the rainbow gathering.
♪ But the trees can't help
their feelings ♪
♪ if they like
the way they're made ♪
Mike, stop it now.
Sorry.
It's the first
richard carpenter music video.
Well, this not putting me
in mind of satan here.
Believe me, it's pretty easy
to put me in mind of satan.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Ha! Let's see christopher atkins
skip a stone like that.
[Mimics bumping sound]
Ow.
You can't eat ham
just anywhere.
You got to find
just the right place.
Ahh, right next
to the dead raccoon.
[Mimics flies buzzing]
Oliver hardy, just eat.
Oops. Ha! Sitting in the water.
That was real easy to avoid.
[Woman giggles]
I'm not going back, jim.
I'm worried that my sandwich
may be small and inadequate.
What's on the spit, pilgrim?
Okay, you selling
herbal essence
or irish spring?
This your pond?
You can take your time.
It's a tough question.
Belongs to my father.
Does your father mind if people
skip rocks across his pond?
Just don't hit
his favorite frog.
I don't think
he's ever mentioned it.
Well, do you want to have
a sandwich?
No. But don't
let me stop you.
Just ram that moldy olive loaf
into your loser face.
- That your car?
- Uh-huh.
Mind if I skip rocks
across it?
Pretty car.
Thanks.
Huh.
Well, I suppose, the plot
is not gonna unfold itself.
Yup!
What's your name?
- Melissa strickland.
- Mine's jodie.
Jodie lee thompson.
Only I don't care
for the lee very much.
Hello.
Hi.
Are we starting over?
Want half a mr. Pibbs?
What are you doing
down by our pond, jodie?
Mellowing out.
Lunch.
You on a journey?
Yes, I guess so.
Not going any place special.
Just drove through
some credits.
That was fun.
Yeah, keep on trucking, I guess.
Guess you'll do your thing,
and I'll do mine.
Yup, whip inflation now. Bye.
You're pretty,
you know that?
Sort of a floppy rhoda way,
I guess.
Yes.
I guess so.
I bet you have
nine boyfriends.
No.
- Six?
- No.
- Three?
- None.
Two! Let me
change my answer.
You're putting me on.
How come?
Well, it's just that
we live on a farm.
We don't raise boyfriends.
None of my business anyway.
What kind of a farm?
We grow walnuts mostly.
Walnuts, huh?
I've never been
on a walnut ranch.
How many head of walnut
do you have?
Can you meet
my needs, please?
What's a matter?
My prize walnut died.
Nothing.
I was just wondering.
Would you like to come up
and see it?
- Uh-oh.
- The ranch?
Why?
Ha! Smooth.
You said you never been on one.
And since you're not going
any place special.
Add to my general fund
of knowledge.
- Will you give me a walnut?
- Yes.
Maybe two.
Well, you can't beat that.
Let's go.
You can help me calf a walnut
if you're lucky.
Man, if she doesn't love him
after riding in his maverick,
- she's a total ice princess.
- Yup.
Surprisingly short
run-on time for a 70's car.
You catch kotter last night?
Mother?
He's the best I can do.
- This is jodie.
- Hello.
He's just
passing through, mama.
Hello, jodie.
Or should I call you buffy?
Supper will be ready
directly.
You look like you could
do with something
besides a chili dog
for a change.
Well, you're right
about that.
- Sit right over there.
- Thank you.
Melissa, go get your father
and tell him
we've got company.
So can you tell me how to get
your daughter in the sack?
She's a pretty girl,
isn't she?
Yes, ma'am, she is.
Yeah, I can't imagine
where she got it.
Where she find you?
Down by the pond.
By the pond?
These walnuts are tearing
through the hay.
What is it?
We have company for supper.
Company? Who?
Nobody you know.
Just a boy I met
down by the pond.
A boy you met?
You brought him
to the house?
Yes, I did. He's nice.
I just want to talk to him,
that's all.
I mean,
I might kill him but--
melissa,
you don't have the right.
The right?
The right to what?
To talk to someone?
Now, don't get so excited.
He's just passing though.
He'll be gone soon.
Is that all there is to it?
Is it?
You didn't call him,
did you?
Or mail anything?
No.
I tell you,
it's all right.
What about lucinda?
She can eat in her room.
Now, come on up to the house.
Or you're grounded, dad.
Herbert von karajan
is not please with that.
Be nice to him.
So you're just
passing through?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm just gonna take
some of this stuff with me.
I'm setting up
a new apartment.
All right,
where's the idiot?
Daddy,
this is jodie thompson.
This is my unbelievably
sweaty dad.
Hello, jodie.
How's uncle bill?
You hungry?
I could eat a horse.
Yeah, I guess I could too.
Good. Have a drink,
young man.
Now, jodie, there won't be
any hard feelings if you
don't want any of it.
- Oh, bosh!
- Oh, hieronymus.
You'll love this stuff.
Best darn cider
in the whole country.
I make it myself.
I put peanuts in it.
Oh, I sure hope
he said peanuts.
Moves out the taste.
You know, with mitchum
you can skip a week.
Did you know that?
Whelp, to b.O.
Man! That's good.
Tastes vaguely
of back sweat.
- Supper ready?
- Just about.
Wash up everybody.
♪ Everybody is working
for the weekend ♪
Whoa! Holy cow.
- [Sighs]
- 'Sup, mike.
Decided to start a walnut ranch
like that guy in the film there.
Man, is that hard work.
Hey, I hear you.
[Sighs]
Man, I barely got started
and look at me.
Hey, you look like hell.
Yeah, I know.
And I was just leafing through
the catalogs.
How do you account for that?
Well, it's darn hard work,
my friend.
Whoa. Man, you said it.
Not gonna make fun
of walnut ranches anymore.
- I'll tell you that.
- No.
[Servo hums]
Oh, mike!
You've been walnut ranching
or something?
Yeah, look at me.
I'm just ragged.
Well, I could've
told you that, man.
Me? I've been pecan farming.
It's like rolling off a log.
Just made
my first million too.
Haven't grown
a single pecan.
- Aah. We'll be right back.
- [Sniffs]
Uh, mike, could you back off?
You smell like canned tamales.
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
[Groans]
Tell me, jodie.
Do you think you'll ever
stop bumming around?
Sure I will, mr. Strickland,
as soon as
the excitement wears off.
Or I find something
I really want.
He wants my hair,
doesn't he?
You know, I gave a lot
of thought to this
before I did it.
I just didn't jump up
and run.
Well, sounds like you know
what you're about son.
I don't actually.
How did you pick that up?
How about another
little drink of my cider?
No, thank you.
Besides, I've got to get
back on the road.
No. Why don't you
wait until morning?
Uh-oh.
Highway's gonna be
foggy tonight.
Melissa, if jodie
wants to leave,
we really shouldn't
try and keep him.
Yes, melissa.
If he has to get
to san francisco--
well, I'm in no hurry.
I just don't want to strain
your hospitality.
Don't be silly.
It's no strain.
And, besides,
we got a spare room.
You can be off first thing
in the morning.
Just mopped up the blood
from the last guy.
I hate to be
any more trouble.
Oh, you are.
- It's no trouble at all.
- To kill you.
Is it, mother?
No, I'll just tell leatherface
you're here.
Of course not.
I'll fix up the sewing room.
The sawing room?
I'll go with you
in case you need any help.
Should we have jodie
as our guest
or should I just drill
right into my molar?
I sure appreciate it.
Don't say anything
more about it.
You and I can
pick up the dishes,
and then we'll
go for a walk.
We pick them up for a second
and set them down.
It's an odd custom.
Do you like living out here
like this in the country?
I suppose so.
The only way I ever lived.
Did you ever want to do
something different?
- Like what?
- Oh, I don't know.
Just something different.
Not everyone can be like you,
you know.
- You're lucky.
- Your death will be quick.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess I am.
But you get to watch the walnuts
grow up wild and free.
- What's it like?
- What?
The steering
on your maverick.
Being able to do exactly
what you want to do
every single day.
- It's exciting.
- Exciting?
- Exciting.
Yes. Why do you think
I turned down your road today?
Why did you?
Because I wanted to see
what was at the other end.
And your end
was at the other end.
I got lucky
because you were there.
Help! Police! Police!
Huh? Girls usually run
a lot farther away from me.
This is where
the fish lives.
- Huh?
- Why did you run?
Because this is where
the fish lives.
Felt like it.
I really wanted to fly,
but I couldn't do that,
so I ran.
You're kind of an idiot
aren't you?
This is where
my tongue lives.
Please, not in front
of the fish.
Um, hey, your hoof
is on my sneaker.
Mmm, that was really bad.
Tell me about yourself.
Who you are, all of that.
Where your fish lives?
Well, my father's
a russian count.
- And when
the bolsheviks came in--
- stop it.
- Don't believe that?
- No.
Well, it could be true.
Stop it.
Oh, sure, ms. "this is
where the fish lives".
Okay.
- My father's a lawyer.
- For the czar's court.
And he wants me
to be a lawyer too.
[Servo]
Stop it.
I told him I didn't know yet.
And I wanted to go out
and poke around the country
for a while.
[Servo] Stop it.
So he gave me the car,
300 bucks, a handshake,
- and here I am.
- Stop it.
Do you let him know
what you're doing?
Sure, I do.
I think he'd like to be with me.
Stop it!
Sounds like a nice man.
Yes, he's a very nice man.
Really crooked lawyer
though, man.
He'll embezzle the socks
right off you.
Hallmark hall of fame presents
the touch of satan.
♪ Come sit with me ♪
♪ and satan too ♪
♪ he's your friend
and mine ♪
You know, I like you.
I did right away.
Like most women.
You like me too, don't you?
Don't you?
Uh-huh.
In a ron palillo
sort of way, sure.
Funny, isn't it?
I wonder what causes
a thing like that.
Maybe I hexed you.
You mean
put the whammy on me?
- Maybe.
- Nope, not me.
I already had whammy
when I was little.
Will you stay here
a few days?
By this log and don't move.
- Huh?
- Stay here with me.
- What?
- Stay here.
- Huh?
I'm lonely, jodie.
I need someone to talk to.
To share things with.
Just for a few days.
Someone to share
clunky dialogue with.
I was going to be in san--
francisco?
What about your folks?
I already live with them.
- Oh, jodie.
- You're such an imbecile.
You know what I mean.
Would they mind?
No.
- All right.
- I'll leave.
Oh, do you know
how long it's been
since I felt this good?
Must at least be 50 years.
No, since the last guys left
about a week ago.
Oh, now he's rubbing
his ryan o'neally face
all over her's.
Let's get up first thing
in the morning.
We can have
the whole day together.
I'll wear my goat's head,
it'll be fun.
- [Laughs]
- What's so funny?
You. You are.
Come on, let's go.
Put on the gloves,
go six rounds,
see what're made of.
Come on, let's go!
Night, fish.
[Servo impersonates fish]
Good night, kids.
Uh, just want to drive through
the director of photography
credit real quick.
Yeah.
Instant ball and chain,
I tell you.
Great bold ones tonight,
huh, honey?
Did you have a nice walk?
Yes, ma'am.
Um, don't come up for
about five minutes, okay?
Good night.
[Man yells on television]
I sure love
the yelling channel.
Your folks seem
nice and evil.
That's your room.
There's ton of varnished bread
laying around in there.
Just push it out of the way.
Nice door. I'd like to see it
crumpled up next to my bed.
Oh, wait.
Ring on my door
in the morning?
- At 6:00?
- Sure, why not?
Okay.
We'll have to get up
and milk the walnuts.
Good night,
creepy vacuous girl.
Uh, so I don't need a kiss
or anything, I'm fine.
[Servo hums]
[Sniffs]
I like to sniff my blinds
before I go to bed.
Hey! Beelzebub, kali,
and lucifer.
They got a signed copy
of the necronomicon here.
"You guys scare me. Ha, ha!
Signed, satan."
Ahh! It's a hideous thing
made out of skin.
Oh, it's just me.
Uh. That represents
all my hang ups, man.
And I just let them fall.
Hmm.
Excuse me,
I think I left a sustacal
back in the corner there.
Must go away.
Who are you?
My name is
margaret rawhide chew.
I usually like
the left side of the bed,
if that's okay.
Huh? Did a plucked turkey
in a wig just talk to me?
Uh, front desk,
there's a mummy in my room.
Uh, mrs. Rotten pumpkin head?
Hello?
- Who is it?
- It's me.
Is captain hook there?
Got to talk to you.
You have a needle? I need
to re-inflate your grandma.
What's the matter?
Is there anybody else
in this house
that I don't know about?
Well, you know about
mrs. Wilma "failed
genetic experiment" right?
Lucinda.
She came right in my room
and scared the hell out of me.
I'm sorry
she frightened you, jodie.
She only kills
when she's crazy.
But you mustn't pay
any attention to her.
She's an old woman and she likes
to wander around the house.
It won't happen again.
Who is she?
She's my great grandmother.
She's not that great.
What happened to her face?
Well, she was badly burned
when she was a young girl.
That's why--
she doesn't go out very much
because of her face.
Unless she's got
a coffee coupon.
Go back to bed.
She was just curious.
I'll go talk to her.
Okay.
Oh, and there's
a huge, insane,
scabby gorilla
wandering around, too.
Why did she say,
"go away"?
She's afraid of strangers.
Well, she wasn't afraid to come
into my room without knocking.
She's an old lady, jodie.
They don't know what they're
doing half the time.
I'll tell you what, I'll go
flip her left turn signal on,
and she'll go
right back to sleep.
I'm sorry.
Go back to bed.
Uh, could you make
your grandma wear a bell?
Okay.
I'm gonna lock the door now.
Do you understand?
I HAVEN'T UNDERSTOOD ANYTHING
SINCE McKINLEY WENT DOWN.
[Mutters]
She's saying, "never try
to deep-fry a snowball."
No, no, it's late.
You have to go to sleep now.
[Mutters]
Tomorrow, I'll take you
for an extra-long walk.
All the way to the dressing
table and back.
You know, there's
a delightful scene
later in the movie where
this old woman raps.
No, there isn't.
Good night.
- And by "good night,"
I mean "shut up.
- ...My sister.
I just wanted to give her
a werthers.
Oh man, now a withered old
billy zane is gonna come in
and give her a withered old
coeur de la mer.
[Servo sighs] Ah, good day.
Took a walk.
Got that dress sewn.
Killed.
A wrinkle!
Huh, well, it's kind of
a lateral move, actually.
She turned into
cecilia bartoli.
I miss my eddie munster
widow's peak.
I still gotta work
on the mustache, though.
Ah, back to being
swifty lazar.
Who's got it going on?
Me, that's who.
What else are we going
to do today?
Would you mind
driving me to town
so I can go to the store?
- Sure.
- Ah, my pet tick.
I'll go change and tell them
we're leaving.
- Meet me at the car.
- Okay.
Aay, I got rooked.
My cup's glued to my lip.
Mom looks like ron popeil.
I asked jodie to stay
a few days, and he agreed.
He agreed that
she asked him?
Figured you would.
Jodie's gonna drive me
to the store.
Does he know
everything we need?
- Yes.
- We'll probably stop by
where the fish lives.
I said jodie's agreed
to stay a few days.
We heard you the first time.
We weren't interested
then either.
And it's all right with you?
No, it's not
all right with me,
but it's your decision,
not mine.
Uh, mike, if you're ever
this family's secret santa,
don't buy them potholders.
That means a great deal
to me, luther.
I mean, "mr. Vandross."
Thank you.
♪ Is this the little demon
I carried? ♪
Go to the store.
Buy canned peaches
and dishwashing liquid.
I should stop
dying my eyebrows.
- Melissa?
- Huh?
What are you gonna tell him?
I don't know.
I'll have to wait and see.
Miking her shoe bottoms?
Well, time to stick my cup
back in my lips.
Oh yeah, he's a hot one,
all right.
Oh, and they don't need
plant holders either, mike.
I mean, you know, if you're
their secret santa.
Got it.
Well, off to my
stewardess job.
You ready to go?
Yeah, let's go.
Take a left right there.
Good.
Look out! Walnut stampede!
Hey, wanna play
pitchfork bug?
Well now, andy, I think
there was a demon
in the car!
Enhance your moody
soundtrack music
with tiny fart sounds.
[All make fart sounds]
He's got two huge sudafed
on top of his car.
- See?
- [More fart sounds]
Huh. From the waist down,
a woman.
Man, I try to keep fit,
but after the third baby.
Um, hi, you seen the other
village people?
Boy, that body pile's
really growing.
Oh, that grandma.
Die die die!
I mean-- hello.
- Well, hello, mr. Mason.
- Howdy, mrs. Strickland.
- Luther around?
- I believe he's around
in the back.
You mind if I wind up
back there?
- Of course not.
- Thank you, ma'am.
He's got a real walnut jones
today, man.
There's not anything
wrong, I hope.
Oh no, mrs. Strickland,
I just wanna
chew the fat with luther
for a while.
I'll be seeing you.
He even brought his own fat.
Hmm, would he even fit
in the iron maiden?
Well, hello, john.
What brings you out this way?
And if you say "my squad car,"
I'll chainsaw you in half.
Oh, nothing much,
just kind of poking around.
- Sit down, take a load off.
- Thank you.
Got the kettle of hands
going, I see.
Luther, doesn't the back
of your place butt up against
- old man larsen's property?
- Mm-hmm, sure it does.
You don't mind if I chew
on this stick insect, do you?
You still working
on that larsen business?
Harris tomley still
got his wind up.
Thinks if we can
break this thing,
he'll be re-elected sheriff
for the next 20 years.
Damn fool.
He's running around
over in newport
like he thought he was
j. Edgar hoover.
Pretty dress, though.
- How can I help?
- Heh.
You mind if I just
take a look around your place?
'Course not.
What're you looking for?
Hell, I don't know.
Ain't found nothing yet.
Not even a suspicious-looking
cow chip.
- Ooh.
- Looks like whoever
killed the old man
went up in a puff of smoke.
I see.
So you don't have any idea
at all who might've done it?
No, nothing.
That's why we're all
just out, poking around.
I guess the sheriff
hopes we'll find
a signed confession
just laying in the grass.
Well, help yourself
to my place, john.
Take all the time you want.
Just don't
spook the walnuts.
Thanks a lot, luther.
I appreciate that.
- Listen.
- My tummy's growlin'.
When you get through poking
around, come on up to the house.
We'll have a touch
of my cider.
I knew you were
gonna say that, luther.
Then give me the finger
like that.
But if sheriff tommy finds out
I was drinking your cider,
I may have to start
working for a living.
Thanks anyway, luther,
I'll see you in ten.
By the way, there's no reason
to look in the crawlspace.
[Servo chuckles]
She's gonna go buy
a whole bunch
of procter & gamble
products.
Why do I suddenly
feel hungry
for carnation ice cream?
I like this place because
they have bulk eye of newt.
Two, three.
And then-- get this-- four!
Morning, mr. Gentry.
Hello, melissa.
Please feel free
to peruse my supply
of unguents, suspensions,
tinctures,
compounded formulas,
and other sundries.
Eh, anyway,
I will shake the paint
off your walls, honey.
What's the matter
with these people?
You'd think we have
the plague or something.
It's not you, it's just me.
Yep, got the plague.
Wanna make out?
They always behave that way.
Well, why?
They say in this town
that I'm a witch.
[Laughs] A witch.
It only rhymes with "witch."
Oh, you plague-ridden
little witch.
Here.
See what I mean?
Witches can't lift flour
on their own.
Why do they think
you're a witch?
Because I am.
Ah, stop it.
You don't believe me?
Ask 'em.
She gives them $15.55
just so she can get
$6.66 back in change.
This is a tense moment
because she used
to date the grocer.
Thank you, melissa.
- You're welcome.
- Then you'll just
deliver the broomsticks
to my house.
Hey, they got a sale
on mismatched beer.
Mm. Steinlager. Pete's.
Zah!
Ah, you made me go burpy.
[Chuckles] I said "zah."
- Young whippersnapper.
- Where's he from?
The grocer's wife died
when someone said "zah."
It's not funny.
- Why'd you do that?
- Serves them right.
You just made it worse,
doing a silly thing like that.
I'm sorry, melissa, but that
sort of thing bugs me.
Come on, let's go.
I've said "zah"
in better towns than this.
After the movie,
remember to pick up
some carnation ice cream!
Okay, here we go.
Anything?
Hmm. Hmm.
Nope, nope, nope,
I'm fine, mike.
I guess all we can do
is add more rocks.
Okay.
You know, I'm worried.
If I wasn't a witch,
I'd be dead by now
or at least shrieking out
a confession
or raining down curses
on my tormentors.
But instead,
hey, I'm great.
I couldn't be better.
Ah. Okay.
Anything?
Oh, no, did you
actually add one?
No, I'm fine.
Very comfortable in fact.
I can't believe this.
Yeah, crow,
what I don't get is,
why do you assume you're
a witch in the first place?
Well, I don't really
assume it, mike,
but I guess it's always been
in the back of my mind.
- You know?
- Hmm, yeah.
Well, you know, crow, the reason
you can survive all of this
is because of your durable
molybdenum frame.
Well, that's nice of you
to say, mike.
But let's face it,
I'm a witch.
You might as well
burn me at the stake.
Oh, crow,
you're not a witch.
But, you know,
it is hard for me
to prove a negative,
you know?
I can't really prove you're
not a frog, for instance.
Mike, this is weird.
Oh, what, you feeling
some pain? Is it working?
No, how'd you know I was
thinking I might be a frog?
Did I tell you that?
No, I mean, I just
used it as an example--
ribbit. I'm a frog! Ribbit.
I'm a frog--
get these rocks off me.
I can't stand this kind of
weight, I'm a tiny frog!
- No, you're not a frog.
- [Alarm blares]
Hey, you guys,
we got movie sign!
Oh, well, help me
with these rocks.
Okay-- whoa!
You know what this means?
I'm not a witch!
I'm a frog!
- Sorry about that.
- You do believe you're
a witch, don't you?
No, I'm a frog.
Oh, we're back here
at the movie.
Yes.
There's no such thing
as witches.
I mean real witches.
Real witches.
Yeah, you know.
The kind they burn.
You are so witchist.
What's the matter?
Would you like to see
where I do my witchcraft?
I do it out of kinko's.
Yeah, I guess so.
Okay, I'll show you
where to turn.
I'm just gonna
stop at this farm
and say "zah"
to somebody, okay?
[Servo hums with music]
Uh-oh, this scene's gonna
play hell on my hay fever.
- This is it.
- [Servo sneezes]
- Wow.
- It doesn't look
very forbidding.
[Servo sneezes]
Why should it be forbidding?
Well, if this is where you
do your witchcraft--
- [servo sneezes]
- Wow.
- Jeez.
Just what kind of witchcraft
do you do?
[Servo sneezes, sniffles]
Oh, I witch the birds
into singing
- and the sun into coming out.
- You all right?
Making everything
look the way it looks.
You're a very lovely witch.
With your soft downy warts.
Come on.
Cabin five is not
on the lake, per se.
You know, if she had
another one of these,
she could be melissa
"two sheds" strickland.
[Mike laughs]
Take a look inside.
Just walk into
the spinning blades.
It's nice.
Wait, you can't use
"amazing grace"
in a devil movie!
- Go on in.
- Okay.
Ooh, lots of pig heads.
Oh, she's a talent agent
for the mormons.
Your own place.
Uh, sorry, that's
the most interesting thing
I could come up with.
Come in here
and shut the door
and leave the world
out there somewhere.
Do you like to turn off
the world sometimes?
No. No, I'm afraid
I might miss something.
Oh, he turns off
the world, all right.
You do, though, don't you?
Yes. Sometimes.
Mostly I just like
to turn off canada.
- Well?
- Shall we trade clothes?
Well what?
Well, do some witch things.
What would you
like me to do?
Um, make me disappear.
Yay!
I wouldn't like to do that.
Make somebody appear, then.
There's been
a walnut uprising.
Hello there.
I must agree with that.
Is lucinda out again?
She wandered into
jodie's room last night.
Scared him half to death.
We'll help you look for her.
You-- you stay here.
Stay here.
Have a good time.
Have some toast
or something.
Poor lucinda.
I'm the only one she
feels comfortable with.
Except her doll.
Mm.
Sad. It really is.
Yep. Really, really,
really sad.
- Okay, sex then?
- What's in the chest?
Beg your pardon?
I'll show you.
Well, hey, a frog
that's not deformed.
Huh, your maverick
is rolling down the hill.
Woo, the sun just
go nova out there?
What's the matter?
I can't take
the pace anymore.
I'm not sure.
- Will you take me
home, please?
- Sure.
Still, that was one of
the snappiest conversations
- they've had yet.
- Mm-hmm.
Welp, obviously a herd
of grandmas came through here.
Ah-hah, I found
the murder weapon.
I'm getting way ahead
of everyone
on this scavenger hunt.
Hey, a giant matchstick.
I could chew on this
for months!
Uh, I thought of a secret santa
gift for these people, mike.
The book how to hide
a murder weapon.
Okay.
[Servo sniffles]
- [Servo sneezes]
- Oh, not again.
Look, here's your allegra.
Oh, thank-- thanks.
- There you go.
- Oh, that was fast.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
Killer grandma got back.
I have a feeling he's gonna
lead a long, full life.
- Yeah.
- [Servo chuckles]
Uh, now I gotta go over
and bust grandpa walton
for raising pot.
Ooh, take three men to peel him
off that seat in hot weather.
Unit one,
this is unit four, over.
I'll hang up and listen.
Unit one,
this is unit four, over.
Unit one's looking
at the radio, giggling.
Unit one, over.
Unit three, do you read?
Do you read?
[Doll] Mama.
Okay, hold still.
Hey, where's my bike?
I reported it stolen
80 years ago!
- Jeez.
- Oh.
What? What?
Well, right about then,
them duke boys showed up.
Lucinda!
Guess who we saw in town?
Be calm.
I suppose you're gonna
blame me for this.
Here's his head,
you've earned it.
I meant to ask him
in for pie.
I don't know
what happened.
Well, you ready
to try that cider?
Hello?
Melissa.
- Oof.
- Ugh.
[Jodie retches]
Whoa, hot dog, french fries,
ramen noodles.
Wow, look at him go.
Melissa.
Go inside with molly.
- Go ahead, go on.
- [Lucinda mutters]
This is so weird, you know,
this happened to me
on one of my first dates.
Grandma killed a guy.
[Bots] Whoa.
Dated the girl
for a while, though.
- [Bots] Oh.
- Yeah.
[Jodie retches]
Um, jodie, that's gonna take
the paint off your car.
Yeah, yeah.
You know,
a vomit stain maverick
was hardly a rarity
in those days.
Mm, I'm here to tell you,
you know?
[Rooster crows]
Did she just crow?
Gross, she's kneeling
in deputy.
Hmm. Killer grandma.
I'm locked in a barn.
Something's not right here.
Why is that pigeon
staring at my head?
[Servo coos]
Well, at least they didn't chain
him to a baldwin brother.
He's got that going for him.
Wow.
Hey, there goes
don "the snake" prudhomme.
Well, the california
bed and breakfast guide
is getting an angry letter.
--Just drive carefully.
We don't wanna be stopped.
Left the p.a. on.
You know, from the back
she looks
exactly like david cassidy.
...now hurry up and follow me
and be careful.
- Hello?
Why don't you just call
harvey keitel over
to fix things?
Why do you think I turned
down your road today?
Why did you?
Because I wanted to see
what was at the other end.
And I got lucky because
you were there.
Huh, I have a weird voice.
They say in this town
that I'm a witch.
They won't find him
until he kills again.
She doesn't go out much
because of her face.
Uh, me, could you
fast-forward?
Can you stay with me
a few days?
Stay here with me?
I'm lonely, jodie.
[Fading] I'm lonely, jodie.
I need someone to talk to.
[Fading] I need
someone to talk to.
To share things with,
just for a few days.
Oh, yep, there--
there's where I tripped up.
Yep.
Um, I've been appointed
as your defense.
So you done
blowing groceries?
Not gonna "zah" your way
out of this one,
are you, pallie?
What're they going
to do about me?
I don't know.
I'm gonna time this pause.
One, two, three, four,
five-- wow.
Five six seven--
will you stay here
until tomorrow?
Well, I do wanna try
grandma's waffles.
I don't seem
to have any choice.
Luther'll unlock that
as soon as he gets back.
They're just pausing
out of spite, now.
- Yeah.
- Trust me
not to run off?
He'll do what I say.
I've got pictures
of him with mom.
Believe me.
Listen, that old woman--
just give us until tomorrow.
Please?
And what good will that do?
It won't change anything.
Maybe I can find a way
for you to understand.
Oh, I understand.
I understand enough
to know that
if you'd gone to that
sheriff ten days ago,
that deputy would
still be alive.
Ah, look, we don't
know he's dead.
She killed that farmer
too, didn't she?
Didn't she?
Did all the actors drink
a quart of robitussin
before shooting?
It's wrong, melissa.
Luther and molly
and you are wrong.
- We're cursed.
- No.
We are cursed.
Come on, we're cursed,
please?
You believe that.
You really do believe it.
Yes.
If I stay until tomorrow,
will you go away with me?
Where?
To the sheriff,
and then, after that,
away from here.
Maybe back to austin
with me.
I can never leave them.
Anyway, I hate line-dancing.
Why? Why, melissa?
What happens to my family
is my responsibility?
And why not luther?
It's his family.
You saw lucinda
this afternoon.
She barely knows
molly or luther
or anyone exists but me.
I saved her.
I'm the only one
that can reach her.
I don't understand.
Much of... anything, really.
Then stay.
Just one more day.
Oh, you mean "staaaaay!"
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, the most
malleable man in the world.
I'll find a way.
Come on, we'll have
a nice murder-free walk.
You really do believe
there's some--
bologna left.
Some devil out there.
Oh yes.
I've seen his food cake.
I suppose that
makes it true.
- [Servo sighs]
- It is true.
Talk! Quicker!
Just like those people
in the store.
They believe you're a witch,
so it's true for them.
Well, I don't,
so you're not.
I'm possessed by the devil.
Michael eisner?
There's no such thing.
I learned that
in community college.
I heard his voice.
He sang "lend me a tenor."
No.
There is no devil.
Huh.
Brought to you by
the national council
for emergency brakes.
I think there used
to be a lake here.
Damn.
Lesson: Never ask
kelsey grammer
to get your gloves
out of your car.
Now he's handcuffed
to the meatloaf.
I just said the steak
was a little tough.
I didn't mean to bring
everyone down.
Ah, so you're
judging us now.
You took too many
pork chops.
I saw a robin today.
I could put my salad fork
right in his jugular.
Well, I'm just gonna
stay through the week,
and that's it.
I'll go lock myself
in the barn.
Don't get up.
Honey, I found the deputy's
badge in my stew.
Oh.
Hmm, need that scottish guy
to come over
and seal up my windows.
Must be hard getting
whale oil anymore
for these lamps.
Check it out, she's dressed
like ed ames.
♪ Skip-a-rope ♪
Dead rubber chicken?
What is that?
Time to go be a general
in the michigan militia.
Oh, I made a terrible
sock monkey.
My obsession with
the color brown
is getting out of hand.
Someone's playing the cicada
in the background.
[All] Oh! Hey!
[All] Aah!
The editor got called out
of the room a lot, I guess.
Can't stop thinking about
that sandwich I had
the other day.
[Servo hums along]
It's the loneliest firefly.
And his friends.
Harpsichord is really
a stupid instrument.
- Wow.
- I'm sorry,
I'm in a bad mood.
Oh, understood.
Binding polymers and you!
[People chant]
Burn the witch!
[Chant continues]
Oh, and go packers too.
But mostly, burn the witch.
"The wicked man
"travaileth with pain
all his days."
...said madeleine.
"And the number of years
is hidden to the oppressor."
Bunch of crap.
"A dreadful song
is in his ears."
It's paula cole, I think.
"In prosperity,
"the destroyer
shall come upon him."
What is it, child?
I heard something.
Pay attention
to the word of god.
For he loves you, and he may
kill you if you don't.
- Yea--
- team.
"The light of the wicked
- shall be put out--"
- by 10:30.
"And the spark of his fire
shall not shine."
Just take the old-fashioned
photo, dad.
"The light shall be dark
"in his tabernacle.
"And his candle
shall be put out with him."
Listen.
Sit back, lucinda.
It's ann eller.
They're coming for me.
Calm yourself, sit back.
So this family has been
pausing for centuries.
- [Servo chuckles]
- It's a tradition.
"The steps of his strength
shall be straightened--"
uh, this does drag,
doesn't it?
"And his own counsel
"cast him down.
- For he is cast..."
- Out of plastic.
[Distant chanting]
Burn the witch!
Ye-- yes?
"For he is cast
into a net..."
And it just
goes on from there.
Oh-- oh, that's right,
I called a service
to come around
and burn my witch.
What is it, david?
It's people saying,
"burn the witch."
You deaf?
Burn the witch!
Papa, what is it?
People saying
"burn the witch"!
Do you have any
deductive powers at all?
I don't know yet.
Take you mother to
the back of the house.
Work her over.
And I'll see what
this is about.
Burn the witch...
It's pretty casual,
it's kind of like
a lake wobegone
witch burning.
[Servo as garrison keillor]
Burning the witch.
Is that you guys
burnin' witches?
Can I come?
Hey, hoss has
lost some weight.
Uh...
We was out burnin', um,
the-- um--
you tell him.
Um, seem kind of silly now.
Good evening, mr. Keitel.
Mr. Strickland.
You've been hittin'
the booze again!
What can I do for you?
Um.
Mrs. Lucasta lost
her young'un tonight.
Only three years old.
Left her at gymboree.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Kester hagen here
lost three head
of cow tonight,
and his wife is down sick.
I'm sorry.
And my souffle fell today.
--Plague.
- I understand.
- Plague.
The plague has hit
near everybody here,
david strickland.
But it ain't hit you.
Now how do you explain that?
Well, I don't comb my hair
with rat bones.
Well, I can only assume--
that I'm franz schubert.
That it's god's will.
Don't talk to us about god,
david strickland.
There's a witch
in that house.
And we aim to have her.
There is no witch
in that house.
Well, my daughter's kind of
a witch, but other than that,
- no witches.
- Go on home!
We will not go home until
we get what we come for.
Your daughter is a witch,
and she's put a hex on us.
That's a damn fool
thing to say, mr. Keitel.
Go on home.
Hah, look at 'em go.
Run, you yellow-bellied--
oh, you're not.
I'll talk to you tomorrow
down at ben procter's store.
There'll be no talk.
We'll have the witch.
Over my dead body!
- Uh-oh.
- So be it.
- Come on.
- Smooth, strickland.
[Strickland screams]
Take my daughter, but spare
my commemorative plates!
Run, lucinda!
[Mumbles]
Aah!
Hey, hey, who are you?
Servo, stop it!
What're you doing?
- Servo, heaven's sake!
- [Servo hums]
Hi, mike, what-- grandma!
Darn it, grandma, stop.
Now, I told you no.
Jeez, I'm sorry, mike.
Wait a minute,
this is your grandma?
Sure is, mike.
Isn't she spry?
When did you get a grandma?
I have two grandmas,
mike, I always have.
The other one doesn't
kill people, though.
This one does.
That's how
I tell them apart.
Now, grandma, down.
Down, grandma.
Uh, I guess it's okay.
I mean, couldn't you
get her a tv or something?
Hold on a second.
What-- what's that, grandma?
Big... slow,
tempting target.
Oh, believe me, I know.
But you just can't, okay?
Well, I tell you what, mike.
I'm just gonna
leave you two alone
to start all over with
each other, all right?
- No, servo, don't.
- Ah, she's full
of stories, mike.
Have a good time.
Hey, hey, get away from me.
We'll be right back.
Back off, lady-- what?
What? I'm sorry,
I didn't catch that.
- [Granny servo screams]
- Ow! Hey, lady!
Stop it! Stop! Now!
Back down! Down! Down!
No, you're hurting me!
Ahh.
Don't these people
have butter to churn?
Taffy to pull?
Prairie lakes to form?
Something.
Please don't
tie me up there!
Quit whining.
Oh! No!
No! No!
Help me!
Let me down from here.
Hey, neil young.
Oh no, you're
making a mistake.
Help me.
Help me, melissa.
Hey, you've been
working out?
You know, maybe
if the amish used buttons
they wouldn't
be so irrational.
No! No!
- Please, you're hurting me!
- No!
- Burn the witch.
- Yeah, that's the plan, amos.
- No!
- Kill the witch.
Kill the witch.
- [Girls scream]
Oh, this is so gauche.
Molly, please help me!
Please don't do this!
[Crowd]
♪ amazing ♪
- Take her down!
- ♪ grace ♪
- Help, somebody help!
- ♪ how sweet the sound ♪
- Damn you!
- Every week we do this!
Anybody, I beg of you!
Anybody, help us!
♪ This song ♪
♪ is in ♪
♪ the public ♪
♪ domain ♪
♪ that's why ♪
♪ we used it ♪
♪ twice ♪
Will you save her?
I say again,
would you save the witch?
Shall I wrap her up
for you?
Yes. Save her.
You've been
hitting the booze?
Will you accept me
as your master?
And go fetch?
Yes. Yes.
Hold up your hand.
Let me stamp it.
Now.
Put out the fire.
Huh.
Caleb, what kind
of charcoal did you use?
Must've got a hold
of a wet witch.
You have asked for death.
And you shall have it.
May your livestock
sicken and die.
Moo-- plunk.
May your crops
rot on the ground.
Happened already.
May your houses be infested
with snakes and scorpions.
Houses? You have houses?
And may your firstborn
be deformed
as pigs and toads!
May your tomatoes
be flavorless!
[Crowd screams]
Let's burn some
beatles records instead!
Did I do okay
with the curses?
I'm open to criticism.
[Servo hums along]
Ooh, ouch, you're--
you're still hot, ow.
You know what,
those villagers
really burn me up.
[Servo chuckles]
It's good I can laugh.
Who are you?
I am the friend
and companion of the night.
I rejoice in spilled blood
- and the baying of dogs.
- [All] Oh.
I wander among
the shades and tombs.
I am gorgo and mormo
of the thousand-faced moon.
But call me sue.
What would you have of me?
I ask...
That you know me
when I return.
I will return.
[Fading] I will return.
Hold on, I'm getting a call
from margot adler.
Gorgo, mormo, you wanna
help me with this knot?
This is the weirdest
big valley ever.
Uh, wish I brought a change
of pants on this trip.
They're all crunchy.
What is keeping me up
tonight?
I had a cup of tea,
a touch of dinner--
oh, right, grandma
mutilated a cop.
That'd do it.
Well, I'm gonna go
puke on the maverick.
- Ahh.
- Okay, everyone
hold it a second.
I just wanna see
if he gets his shoes on.
Ye-- yes. Yes.
Great. Glad they
showed that to us.
Gah!
Where'd they find
the 590-watt light bulb?
I actually need
something meat-hooked.
I'm gonna go see
if grandma is up.
Yep, I think he still has
those shoes on, you guys.
I can hear them.
- I'm gonna keep my eye
on the situation.
- Thanks mike.
- I'll let you know.
- Good, good.
Well, hey, look.
Grannies do swing
on the outhouse door
without their nighties.
Uh, he's got the shoes on
here, this is good.
Little bit of redundancy
on the shoes is good, mike.
I'm gonna
back you up on this.
Thanks.
You know, unless
there is a change
I think we can just assume
he's wearing the shoes
- from now on.
- Yeah, yeah, good.
Maybe this was
once fast-paced,
and someone spilled
a grape nehi on it,
and it got all gummy.
Maybe.
I realized we hadn't had
a stuttering conversation
for several hours.
He rejoices
in spilled blood
and the baying of dogs.
Marilyn manson?
He is gorgo
and mormo.
♪ And joe ♪
If you can hang on a sec,
I'm about to say something.
Jodie,
you turned down
the road yesterday
because you wanted to see
what was up the other end.
Just like that chicken.
Well, now you've seen it.
But you won't believe it.
I can't.
- Not can't. Won't.
- Ah.
You won't believe
in the devil
because you're afraid
if you believe in him,
he'll be real.
It's like when you wouldn't
believe in peanut butter.
He is real.
I heard him.
I felt him inside me.
That was acid reflux.
It's not true.
Face it.
I've had to.
Do you think I like it?
Do you think i've
enjoyed all these years
with the devil's
spirit inside me?
Sure, we've had some laughs.
It happened, jodie.
Just like in your dream.
That dream was coincidence.
Is it a coincidence
that I know they sang
a hymn in your dream?
The good christians
sang a good christian song
while they were
burning my sister.
And they didn't even have
a youth horn section.
♪ Amazing ♪
♪ grace-- ♪
♪ and chuck ♪
♪ the sound ♪
♪ that saved ♪
♪ a wretch-- ♪
♪ like me
public domain ♪
♪ we don't have to pay anyone
ha-ha-ha-ha ♪
What're you doing to me?
♪ It's that witchcraft! ♪
♪ Wicked witchcraft ♪
Why is it
so important that
I believe in this
devil of yours?
Well, I get a commission.
Because you can save me.
I've got a sickness
in me, jodie.
I've got occasional
devil worship.
You can free me from it.
But not unless you
believe it exists.
Aren't there any jesuits
in the phone book?
Come on.
How can I help you?
What can I,
a single puss, do?
- By believing what
I've told you--
- mm-hmm.
And what I'm going
to tell you.
Let me pause to drench
my next line in meaning.
I want to help you.
But I'm really busy
right now.
I love you.
And I've grown awfully fond
of your grandma.
May I touch your sideburn?
Then hear the rest of it.
I want to help.
Consarn it, break it up!
My dagnabbit
contract with satan!
Wow, poop deck pappy
getting all upset here.
They turned me down
for that policy!
They said it
couldn't happen!
[Servo mutters]
No!
I told you I could
take you, you pansies!
I could take
the whole family!
- Wow.
- [Crow chuckles]
- Can't believe I have
to wash satan's towels.
- Melissa.
- Crossroads seem
to come and go.
If all this were true,
that would make you
127 years old.
- Yes.
- Man, she's getting
into strom thurmond country.
[Servo does train bell]
It's the train going
through the pause.
Is this still
the same pause,
or is it technically
a sub-pause?
Even if it were true,
I'd love you anyway.
I mean, I'd put you
in a home, but...
Ugh.
Hey, john quincy adams!
[Grandma screeches]
- Wow.
- Run, jodie.
Grandma used to work
for the l.a.p.d.
Witch!
Oh!
- Oops.
- Oh no.
Burn, witch, burn.
Oh, and grandma had
just gotten a job
as a greeter at wal-mart.
[Distant crowd]
♪ amazing grace ♪
Hey, mike, what were you guys
doing during the 70's?
Making witch movies?
Inhaling huge clouds
of marijuana?
Big, ugly flared pants on?
We had to do something.
Melissa, come on!
Oh, she'll be fine, come on.
[Song continues]
I know, when
you're that age,
you're just ready
to go right up.
The slightest spark
can get it going.
Let me tell you.
Aw, now she's melissa
"no sheds" strickland.
Man, never let edie sedgwick
borrow your lake cabin.
I've done it. No good.
Look at it go, grandma
must've exploded or something.
Man.
[Song continues]
Grandma's flash-paper
bathrobe
turned out to be a mistake.
Oh, if the septic tank
goes up,
we're all in trouble.
In the wake of the tragedy,
the town built
a better grandma.
Stronger,
with a steel frame,
and a sprinkler system.
Now I just have to watch out
for my other grandma.
She's really crazy.
Mm-- ugh.
You think I wanted
your saliva?
Is that why you did that?
Hmm, not worth it.
Sorry.
I had fun, though.
See ya.
Can you not french my daughter
during breakfast?
Goodbye, sir.
Thank you for trusting me.
I'll keep my word.
I'll tell no one
of your backsweat problem.
Well, let's lock you
back in the barn.
I'll walk out
to the car with you.
Could you drop me off
at tanglewood?
I'm conducting mahler's 10th
this weekend.
Open the lens more.
We need more light!
More!
Mm, I see grandma
behind that tree.
You might wanna
make a run for it.
I just wanted to ask you,
while we're away
from all the others,
do you think
we're weird at all?
It's all true, you know,
everything she told you.
I'm sorry, sir,
I can't believe that.
And I can't believe she's
possessed by the devil, either.
I suppose not.
Whatever.
Be careful.
Goodbye, jodie.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Oh, and, uh,
don't join al pacino's
law firm.
May the dark one hold
your soul in his clutch--
I mean, uh, safe trip.
Yo.
Eh, nice kid.
Well, the bomb should go off
in a couple of minutes.
[Servo hums along]
Ahh.
Fritz kreisler used to wear
a striped shirt like that.
Sorry, I got so many
walnut husks in my teeth.
Well, I should say goodbye
to the fish, I suppose.
Where the heck is that
village smithy?
[Bots hum, whistle]
I am hungry,
but I can't go back
to the grocery store
after that "zah" incident.
[Servo hums]
Wow, look at the smoke.
Everybody must be burning
their grandmas today.
[Servo hums along]
Hey, I ran out of gas.
I'm kind of a wolf when
I'm alone with myself.
Yep.
Hey, the odometer's
all sixes.
Wait a minute,
where's my immortal soul?
Oh crap, I left it
back at the farm.
We're back at the beginning.
This film is
a mobius strip.
My fish moved
and didn't leave
a forwarding address.
See, I don't get
how they billed this
as a "rollicking musical."
No.
The only known shots
of bigfoot in a t-shirt.
Come, sit in the crotch.
Well-- you know,
the tree...
Right.
Draw.
I love you, melissa.
Almost as much as I love
wide-whale corduroys.
It doesn't matter that
the devil's in your soul.
Yeah, look familiar, mike?
Yeah-- hey.
I love you.
Uh, are you blowing me off,
or is this just
one of our pauses?
Our next pause
is gonna be this big.
Ready, wrestle!
The devil just happens to be
peeking out of
her mouth right now.
"Hu--hey!
Get out of there!"
Well, their dates are easier
without grandma
clubbing him to death.
Huh?
Man, I thought
I was an operator.
- He's fast.
- Whoa.
You know, my mom used
to have a little saying.
It's just as easy
to fall in love
with a woman who's not
possessed by the devil.
Mm-hmm.
I have one chest hair.
Okay, kids, the picnic
is this way, w-- aah!
Aah!
You freed me.
I've turned into
gloria stuart at last.
I love you, melissa.
I do love you.
But why are you
sanding my shoulder?
You seem to have some sort
of tarp on your hand.
You see, you're gonna have
to expect a little of this
- with your brides of satan.
- Oh yeah.
I should know.
What's wrong?
Your face.
Well, what's wrong
with my face?
Well, nothing, if you
like eubie blake.
Oh my god.
I've become
sigourney weaver.
He cheated me.
He never told me.
Man, if you can't
trust the devil...
Jodie, i--
I'm going to die.
- No.
- You're 127 years young.
There's a way.
No.
Jodie, not that way.
What would you have of me?
Don't let her die,
I love her.
Oh boy, no I don't.
Will you accept me
as your master?
Yes.
No. No.
- Then save her.
- Morley safer.
Hit him.
Quickly now, save her.
Well, I guess that's what
I was calling you for, devil.
Ugh.
I should've asked
the devil to throw in
some other modifications
while I was at it.
Good, so we're both
in the clutches of the devil
because you wanted seconds.
And they drift apart
after three weeks.
Uh, we're gonna have
a litter of jackals
in nine months, you know.
This is a good pause
we're having, huh?
You know, I'm guessing
this guy's gonna be
a fairly minor soldier
in the devil's army.
Probably have a tiny picture
- in hell's newsletter.
- Yep.
They'd better book
a hall in hell
for their unholy wedding.
It's like a year wait.
Oh, I don't know,
I don't trust this, mike.
I just think this
is the longest pause yet.
[Mike chuckles]
Okay.
So, in the end,
satan wins, I guess.
Yep, pretty much
a shut-out for satan.
Yep.
Aah, the devil!
Let's get out of here.
[Mike moans]
Sweet deal.
Hey, hey mike!
I just sold
my soul to satan.
Oh, you did?
So I'm probably
gonna have lots
of unfathomable
worldly power real soon.
Yeah, I thought I'd give you
the heads-up on that.
Oh, that's real thoughtful
of you, thanks, crow.
Yep, got a contract
right here.
From satan.
Let me see that.
"Shall take possession
of his mortal soul."
Yeah, that all scans.
Oh, but look at this.
Little mistake here.
Looks like you
sold your soul to stan.
- Not satan.
- Huh.
- Yeah.
- Well, there's
a number there.
- Would you mind
calling it, please?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- Wow.
- Yeah, see, this--
this isn't even
the area code for hell, so--
- ah.
- Yello? Stan johnson.
Ah, see, there you go.
Hi, stan, this is,
uh, mike nelson.
- You're not by any chance
the devil, are you?
- Uh, nope.
I'm a cpa and investment
consultant.
- Damn.
- Ah-hah. Yeah.
Hey, I'm calling on behalf
of a crow t. Robot.
Oh, right.
Little, skinny gold guy?
Kind of bug-eyed? Sure.
Yeah, that's the guy.
Hey, did you buy his soul?
Yes, I did.
I manage a well-balanced
portfolio of souls.
They can be
very high-yield.
Um-- um, stan, this is crow.
When can I get my soul back?
Is that possible?
Oh, I'm sorry, I resold
your soul already
to citycorp in
a big block of souls.
Uh, man, I am gonna
have to make
so many phone calls
to get my soul back.
Oh man-- oh, and pearl's
babysitter is calling.
Hello?
Be with you in a minute.
Almost finished story time.
Then everyone goes to sleep.
Uh, can I come out now?
Shush, bad dog. Go to sleep.
Okay.
Now, where was I, brian?
Oh, uh,
the tall fellow
was repeatedly refusing
to ingest
green eggs and ham.
The short fellow was
bizarrely insistent upon it.
Yes, very good.
Yeah.
"I will not eat them
in a plane.
I will not eat them
on a train."
"On a train."
Right, you know,
why doesn't he just
leave him alone?
He has pointedly
made his refusal
to eat this dish clear.
The mere hypothetical
changing of a location
is irrelevant and tedious.
And-- and that sam I am
is so bloody repetitive
I could scream.
Are we a little
cranky, brian?
No, madam, I am overtired.
So I shall turn in now.
So if you wouldn't mind,
please.
My blankie.
My nookie.
And my friend.
Oh. Thank you kindly.
Good morrow to you.
Nighty-night.
Well, now, me?
I'd definitely
eat them on a train.
Quiet, no bark.
--Delicious on a train,
but a plane?
I'd have to think
about a plane.
Maybe substitute
bacon for ham.
That sounds kind of nice,
and we could have a--
oh-- oh boy.
[Bobo chirps]
- No bark.
- [Thumps]
Ow! I'm not barking.
I was just talking-- ow!
I'm commenting on the story.
There's no barking
involved at all.
- No, no bark.
- [Thump]
Ow! No, I'm not sure
you see my point.
Here, it's like this.
Rather than barking,
as you assumed,
I was actually--
- [thump]
- Oh, come on!
...talking, i'm-- ow!
- No!
- Ow!
- No bark.
Ow! I'm not barking,
i'm-- ow!
- Bad dog.
- [Bobo mumbles]
- Jeez! Ow-- ow!
- Bad dog.
Ow! Stop it!
This is where
the fish lives.